<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>MuST Tutorial</title>
    <link>https://www.must-tutorial.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on MuST Tutorial</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 13 Jul 2020 20:33:24 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.must-tutorial.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>First time logging in</title>
      <link>https://www.must-tutorial.com/howto/first_log/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jul 2020 20:33:24 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.must-tutorial.com/howto/first_log/</guid>
      <description>The hub has MuST and ASE installed. Each user gets their own Jupyter Notebook environment on the hub.
 Click on &amp;ldquo;Hub&amp;rdquo; to connect to the JupyterHub. The login page will open in a new tab. Enter your username  Choose a password (remember this password for future logins!) Click &amp;lsquo;Sign In&amp;rsquo; Wait for your server to start  While your server is starting, you will see the following message:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cloning a git repository</title>
      <link>https://www.must-tutorial.com/howto/cloning/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2020 20:33:24 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.must-tutorial.com/howto/cloning/</guid>
      <description>Open a terminal by clicking on New -&amp;gt; Terminal
your terminal will open in a new tab. To clone a git repository, use git clone followed by the address of the repository. You can clone an example MuST notebook using the following command:
git clone https://github.com/hkershaw-brown/example_notebook.git Cloning the repository successfully will look like this:
On your JupyterHub page you will now the the example notebook folder.
Clicking on example notebook will take you into the example notebook direcory, where you will see example_must_ase.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Troubleshooting</title>
      <link>https://www.must-tutorial.com/howto/restarting/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jul 2020 14:41:53 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.must-tutorial.com/howto/restarting/</guid>
      <description>Clicking on Control Panel will take you to the following page
You can stop your server, then start your server again
To get back to your sever from this page click My Server</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Useful Documentation</title>
      <link>https://www.must-tutorial.com/docs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jul 2020 20:33:24 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.must-tutorial.com/docs/</guid>
      <description>Here are some external links that you may find helpful:
ASE calulcator for MuST by Amish Chovatiyas Jupyter Notebooks Python MuST ASE </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://www.must-tutorial.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jul 2020 20:29:15 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.must-tutorial.com/about/</guid>
      <description>This project was created for a MuST workshop at LSU. The JupyterHub runs on Jetstream - the NSF cloud. The MuST JupyterHub project was part of the XSEDE Campus Champions Fellows Program The image used to run the hub is ubunutu 18.04 with MuST, ASE and all their dependencies installed.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>